欢迎加入OCR小组 qq群906722936 字幕优先发布于群内
两块带骨的 两块长排
Two chops, two strips.
快把我的肉送来
Run me my meat!
是 主厨
DAVE: Yes, Chef!
我利用各种线索
I used context dlues
推断出你需要更多牛排
to figure out you needed more steaks.
麻烦你把这个端过去 别再说 是 主厨
Uh, would you put these out and stop saying, "Yes, Chef"?
是 主厨
Yes, Chef.
抱歉 主厨
Sorry, Chef.
场面搞挺大啊
Quite a yardecue you're throwing.
宝贝 咱得好好庆祝一下
Oh, babe, we had to celebrate.
熔丝盒公司终于开始盈利了
I mean, the Fuse Box is finally in the black.
真是谢天谢地 但也没那么盈利
Hallelujah! Look, not that black.
利润只有611刀
Your profit was only $611.
-那也是利润  -好吧
That's still a profit. Well, yeah.
结果你决定庆祝一下
Then you decided to go and celebrate
买了个价值一千的烤架
and buy a thousand- dollar grill.
千万别在我的烤架旁说它坏话 蒂娜
Oh. Ooh! No negative talk around my grill, Tirai
提个醒要找就不会吃那个土豆沙拉
And by the way, Iwouldn't eat that potato salad.
是金小姐做的
Miss Kim made it.
比回味更糟的
The only thing worse than the aftertaste
是吃它时候的味道
is the taste- taste.
我还以为是鸡蛋沙拉
I thought it was egg salad.
离远点
Hey, get away from that.
戴夫 你那19个口袋里
Dave, do you have any Worcestershire
有伍斯特酱吗
in one of your 19 pockets?
没有 但我有更好的
No, but I've got something even better.
看 非动物测试 低盐 小批量生产
Check this out. Cruelty- free, Iow- sodium, small- batch,
当地采购 纯手工 利于心脏健康
locally- sourced, artisanal, heart- healthy rub.
你说这是纯手工的
You say it's artisanal?
对 怎么了
Yeah, yeah. What?
身手还在 格罗弗
Still got it. Hey, Grover?
-过来  -有什么事吗 卡尔文先生
Come here. What do you need, Mr. Calvin?
能去趟街角的店
Would you run to the corner store
帮我买点伍斯特酱
and get me some Worcestershire,
一袋冰 再买张彩票
a bag of ice, and play my number for me?
数字是697
Six, nine, seven.
直选还是组选
Straight or boxed?
直选 去吧
Straight. Go on now.
我跟你一起去
I- I'|I go with you.
珍玛 你儿子都十几岁了
Uh, Gemma, your son's a teenager now.
他能自己走去克雷斯海文
He can walk to Cresthaven by himself.
你说得对
You're right Hmm.
我怎么成一个十几岁孩子的妈了
How did I become the mother of a teenager?
那是因为2010年
Well, it was 2010, and we were riding high
我们在邦妮·莱特音乐会玩得太嗨了
from that sexually charged Bonnie Raitt concert.
顺理成章的就
One thing led to another, and
对 我记得那晚
Yeah, yeah, I remember the night.
我是说他都这么大了 我还没觉得自己变老了
I just mean, he's grown so much, and I don't feel older.
但我的胃好像不太好了
Although my stomach's not feeling great.
我刚吃了点金小姐的面包布丁
Oh, I just had some of Miss Kim's breadl pudlding.
我还以为是什锦菜卷
I thought those were enchiladas.
那是土豆沙拉
It's potato salad,
我觉得那玩意该丢了
and I think we need to throw that out.
乐意之至
Gladly.
老爸 抱歉 我们来晚了
Hey, Pop. Sorry we're late.
我们刚在厄尼家 跟熔丝盒员工
Yeah, we were at Ernie's at the trivia tournament
一起参加智力竞赛 你也应该来的
with the Fuse Box staff. You should have stopped by.
马蒂 我可不是员工
Well, Marty, I'm not staff,
你们也不是
and neither are you.
我们是管理层
We're management.
你们不该这样界限不分
You shouldn't be blurring the lines like that.
别这样 爸 我要是没去
Oh, come on, Dad. What would they have said
他们会怎么说
ifIdidn't show up?
他们会说 你是老板你说了算
They would say that you're the boss.
但我不是那种只管人的老板
Yeah. Im Im not like a...Im not like a boss boss.
我是个搞笑的老板
I'm a fun boss.
马尔科姆也在场
Malcolm was there.
马尔科姆 告诉老爸我当时多搞笑
Malcolm, tell Daddy how fun I was.
没错 老爸
Oh yeah, Pop
他们整天都在取笑马蒂
They were making fun of Marty all day.
不是取笑 是搞笑
Not"fun of. "Fun with. "
马蒂 你不可能跟所有员工都成为好兄弟
Marty. You can't get all buddy- buddy with the employees.
听着 我干这行很久了
Listen, I've been doing this for a long time,
我是来赚钱的 不是来取悦大家的
and I'm in it to make money, not be popular.
老爸 还好你这么想
Yeah, well, I'm glad to hear you say that, Pop,
因为从他们谈及你的方式来看
because from the way they were talking about you,
你确实不太受欢迎
you are definitely not popular.
注意后面
Behind!
-主厨 我有话不知能不能讲  -不能
Chef, if I may. You may not.
我本来是打算同意你观点的
Well, I was actually going to agree with you.
那你继续
Oh. Proceed.
在退伍军人事务部 我们会强制性举办
Down at the VA, we ve had a series
长达三小时的健康工作场所研讨会
of mandatory three- hour, healthy workplace seminars,
这主意很棒
which, by the way, are fantastic.
但依我愚见 应该改成6小时
In my opinion, they should be six hours.
总之 我从中学到
Anyway, what I've learned
适当的管理力度对健康的工作场所
is that properly managing power dynamics is crucial
是至关重要的
to a healthy workplace.
戴夫 就冲你这句话
Huh. Well, Dave you know, for that,
你可以给牛排翻个面
you get to flip the steaks
是 主厨 谢谢 主厨
Yes, Chef. Thank you, Chef.
抱歉 主厨 不对 是卡尔文
Sorry, Chef. Sorry, Calvir
你们吃完了我的芝上三豆沙拉
Y'all finished my cheesy, three- bean salad.
还好我多带了一此
Good thing I got some more.
她刚是从她的座椅里拿出来的吗
Did she just pull that out of her seat?
恶心 真是恶心
Nasty. Just nasty.
欢迎来到这个小区 跟我们做邻居
♪Welcome to the block, welcome to the neighborhood ♪
欢迎跟我们做街坊
♪ Welcome to the hood. ♪
-真是好极了  -可不是吗
This is great Oh, isn't it?
不 马蒂
No, Marty.
我看见大家都在吃喝聊天
I see people eating and chatting
玩平衡车 刷抖音
and hoverboarding and TikTok- ing,
-你知道我没看见什么吗  -什么
but you know what I don't see? What?
没看见人工作
People working.
我们公司是修理电车的
Our company repairs electric vehicles.
电车都在那边
The vehicles are over there.
而我付钱雇来工作的人
The people that I'm paying to work on them
都在这边 除非他们都在一个地方
are over there, but we don't make money
否则我们没法赚钱
until they get together here.
爸 对我们这代人来说
Dad, for people in my generation,
工作与生活平衡是关键
work- life balance is key.
一边工作一边玩 工作就是这样做的
People work while they play. That's how work gets done.
才不是
That's not what work is.
兄弟
My man.
工作就不是玩乐的地方
Work isn't supposed to be fun.
所以才称之为工作
That s why they call it"work"
这个词来源于拉丁语 粗壮的臀大肌
It comes from the Latin"Bustus thy gluteus maximus. "
It comes from the Latin- "Bustus thy gluteus maximus. "
早上好 巴先生
Morning, Mr. B
你好啊 书呆子
What up, nerd?
考特尼
Courtney.
这是怎么回事
What the hell was that?
别激动 爸
Oh, Dad, come on.
我跟考特尼是老朋友了
Courtney and I are old friends.
我们一起在喷气实验室工作了好多年
We worked together at JPL for years.
但你们不再是同事了 懂吗
Well, you're not coworkers anymore, all right?
现在她给你打工
She works for you now.
如果你一直把这里当成游戏餐厅
This place will never be productive
公司就永远不会产生效益
if you keep treating it like a Dave &Buster's.
好吧 爸
Okay. Dad,
Okay. Dad
我是这家公司的共同所有人
I am co- owner of this company.
我对怎么运作有发言权
I have a say in how things are run.
这里怎么会是游戏餐厅
And this- this is hardly a Dave&Buster's.
这个要放哪 老板
Where do you want this, boss?
-还有足球桌  -放那边
A foosball table? Right over there.
把这个退了 我是老板
Take it back to the store. I'm I'm the boss.
我是老板
CALVIN: I'm the boss.
这是我买的
Well, I ordered this.
退了 拉走
Take it back. Got to pull it.
别 兄弟
My man. My man.
我当时就直叫唤
And so Iwas like, "Ow, ow, ow! "
然后就脱下鞋子
And that's when I took off my shoe
才发现不是鹅卵石
and I realized it wasn't a pebble.
是水果糖
It was a Skittle.
你扔了吗
Which you threw away?
扔了 扔进我嘴里了
Sure. In my mouth.
我就多余问你
Aw. Why did Ieven ask you?
Aw. Why did I even ask you?
这下好了 我们要快点
Oh, great. Let's hurry.
为什么
Why?
这些建筑工人跟女人说话
It's just that construction workers aren't very enlightened
-不太文明  -好吧
when it comes to women. Okay.
-打扰一下  -别理他们
Hey, excuse me? Jyst ignore them.
你的罐头（胸）
Your cans!
你还真有创意呢
Wow. Original.
你要我去拿吗
You want me to grab'em?
想得美
In your dreamsl
好吧
Okay, well,
你的桃子罐头掉在路上了
your- your peaches fell out onto the sidewalk.
你是指这些啊
Oh, you mean those cans?
好的 我来拿
Yes, I will take those.
-谢谢  -不客气
Thank you. Hey, no problem.
祝您愉快 太太
Have a great day, ma'am.
太太
Ma'am?
我听着挺文明的
Seemed pretty enlightened to me.
你懂什么 你连掉鞋里的糖都吃
What do you know? You eat candy out of your shoe!
不是吧 爸 打卡钟
Really, Dad? A time clock?
正如你所言 我们都是老板
Well, as you say, we're both bosses.
所以如果你决定
So if you decided
给员工一台足球桌 那行
to let the employees have a foosball table, fine,
但我不会付钱让他们玩
but I'm not going to pay them to use it.
所以他们要玩的时候先打卡下班
So now they clock out when they start playing,
玩完了 再重新上班
and when they're done, they clock back in.
好了 各位
Here you go, everyone.
你们现在已经打卡下班了
You guys are all clocked out.
就像你们喜欢说的 燥起来吧
So as you guys like to say, turn up.
你不是真的这样做吧
You aren't really doing this.
这是怎么了
What's going on?
麦片自助关闭了
Oh, the cereal bar is closed.
你如果9点还没来
If you're not here by 9: 00 a. m
就错过了早餐
you miss breakfast.
爸
Dad.
麦片自助提供的不仅是早餐
Cereal is not just for breakfast.
对啊 巴先生 我们九零后
Yeah, Mr. B, us millennials are really
特别喜欢优化我们的新陈代谢
into hacking our metabolisms,
所以会吃很多小型餐
so we eat a lot of micro meals.
那就叫吃零食
That's just snacking.
你们这代人不能乱改名
Your generation can't rename snacks.
零食我懂
I know snacks.
我也吃得很猛
I've been a snacker.
我吃零食的历史堪称光荣
I'm from a long line of snackers.
我背包里也曾零食汹涌 四押
I keep a snack in the backpack, Jack.
这么说你想让那些人调戏你
So, you wanted these men to hoot at you?
当然不是 好恶心
No, it's gross.
我只希望他们想要调戏我
Ijust want them to want to hoot at me.
我是说
I mean,
连建筑工人都对我没兴趣了
when you lose construction workers
珍玛 听听你自己说了些啥
Gemma, listen to yourself.
我知道 听起来不可思议
I know. I know it's crazy, but
但好像才不久前
it just seems like a minute ago,
我还跟高中同学在玉米地里参加啤酒聚会
I was at a kegger in a cornfield with my high school friends,
把洒言欢 跟男孩跳艳舞 还试着骑牛
drunk, dirty dancing with boys, trying to ride cows.
不喜欢这个故事
Not loving this story.
骑牛什么意思
What do you mean, "ride cows"?
就是骑牛呗 我们是最酷的
We rode cows. We were the cool kids.
但问题是
But the point is,
突然间 我就被人称作太太了
all of a sudden, here Iamgetting"ma'am- ed. "
真遗憾 亲爱的
Oh, I'm sorry, honey.
我还记得我第一次被叫太太 也挺难过
I remember my first ma'am. It was tough.
但我那时比你年纪大
But I was older than you, though.
-我就是这个意思  -但只有我
That's what I'm saying. But I'm the only one
以前经营过公司 马蒂
who's run a company before, Marty.
爸 我知道 但你还沉浸在过去
I know, Dad, but you're stuck in the past.
戴夫 给你兄弟讲讲道理
Dave, talk some sense into your man.
出什么问题了
What's wrong?
哪哪都是问题
What's right?
没有一个员工尊重他
None of his employees respect him.
其中一个还从他手里抢走甜甜圈
One of them snatched a donut out of his hand
叫他书呆子
and called him nerd.
也不是不对
Not inaccurate.
但也不是很合适
But not appropriate, either.
戴夫 快帮我说说
Come on, Dave, back me up.
保持办公环境休闲自在
Well, uh, keeping office dynamics informal
是可以促进协作 但是
can foster collaboration, but
领导也确实需要清晰的组织阶层
leadership does require a clear organizational hierarchy
来推动决策
to facilitate decision making.
意思就是 我是对的 对吧
Translation: I'm right, right?
是 主厨
Yes, Chef.
你不懂
You don't understand.
考特尼跟我是很长时间的朋友
Courtney and I have been friends for a long time.
对 有福利的那种
Yeah. With benefits.
什么
Say what? Huh?
马尔科姆 你怎么不用喇叭喊
Malcolm, what kind of whisper was that?
得了吧 马蒂 老爸不知道福利啥意思
Come on, Marty, Pops doesn't know what benefits means.
我当然知道
Oh, yes, I do
是指养老金 医保 或上床
It means pension, health care, or smashing.
我也知道她又不可能给你上医保
And I know she didn't give you health care.
那是几个月前的事了
Look, it it was a couple of months ago.
我跟考特尼和之前喷气动力实验室
Courtney and I were out
的同事参加了一个问答之夜
for a trivia night with the gang from JPL.
对 你知道吗 爸
Oh, yeah, you know, Pop.
他也拉着我去了
He made me come join the team,
那些书呆子连我名字都不问
and those geeks didn't even learn my name.
一直叫我“体育男”
Kept calling me"Sports Guy. "
马尔科姆 你先别打断
Malcolm, do you mind?
就是说 这也太侮辱人了吧
I'm just saying, that's insulting, okay?
我不仅懂体育知识
I know more than just sports- -
我还懂历史
I know history,
我懂哲学 我也懂什么时候该坐下
I know philosophy, I know when to sit the hell down.
总之比赛到了最后一刻
Anyway, the contest was down to the wire,
考特尼正确地
and Courtney correctly
说出了海绵宝宝的种属
identified SpongeBob's species:
多孔滤食性生物体
Aplysina fistularis.
多厉害 然后一来二去
Damn. You know, one thing led to another.
我知道会怎样 我有两个儿子
Yeah, I know what it led to. I have two sons.
第二天早上 我们意识到不合适
The next morning we realized this wasn't us.
还是做朋友比较好
We're better off as friends.
对 但是马蒂 事实是
Yeah, but, Marty, the fact is,
你和员工上床了
you slept with an employee
不不不 我绝对不会
No, no, no, I would never.
我是在上床之后雇的她
I hired her after we slept together.
因为你们上床了吗
Because you slept together?
不 她是一位杰出的工程师
No, no. She's a brilliant engineer.
只因为我们上过床 就拒绝掉这样的人才
Would it have been fair to reject her
岂不是不公平
because we slept together?
不不不 那也很糟糕
No. No, no, no. That would be bad, too.
这个故事怎么讲都很难听
Every version of this is bad.
马尔科姆 放那边去就行
Malcolm, just set those over there.
好
All right.
哟 这里看着真不错
Wow, the place is looking good.
大家都去哪儿了
Where is everybody?
不知道 也许马蒂跟他们都睡过
I don't know. Maybe Marty's sleeping with all of them.
这也没啥大不了的
It's not that big of a deal.
当然有了 蒂娜 这很棘手
Yes, it is, Tina. It's messy.
有些底线是不能逾越的
There's some lines that shouldn't be crossed.
你不该知道你同事裸体的样子
Like knowing what your coworkers look like naked.
没人来上班了 爸爸
Well, no one's here, Dad.
瞧你做了什么
See what you did?
还是瞧瞧你做了什么吧
I think it's see what you did.
fvsabox
People think they can just show up for work anytime they want.
让大家以为这个班想什么时候来上都行
不是 爸 三个工程师去外面的小吃车
No, Dad, three of our engineers are at a taco truck
买早餐墨西哥卷饼了
getting breakfast burritos
因为你关闭了麦片自助
because you closed the cereal bar.
有两个程序员去另一家科技公司面试了
And two of our programmers have job interviews
因为人家有空中曲棍球
at another tech company where they have air hockey
和无限量的冷萃
and unlimited cold brew on tap.
你给我打住 在工作时间喝酒
See, right there. Drinking on the job?
这就是越界
That's crossing the line.
冷萃是指冷萃咖啡啊 宝贝
Cold brew is coffee, baby.
你从哪读到的《红迪报》吗
Where did you read that, babe, on the Reddit?
爸爸 那是红迪网
Daddy, it's just Reddit.
马尔科姆 你那晚智力问答表现好出色
Hey, Malcolm, great job at trivia the other night.
我们终丁有个懂体育的了
It's so great to finally have a sports ringer.
我们终于有个懂体育的了
你那书呆子弟弟一点忙都帮不上
Because, you know, your nerd brother is no help.
你知道吗 考特尼
Yeah, you know what Courtney?
我不只是个棒球教练
I am not just a baseball coach.
没错
Mm. Yeah.
不如你问我一个聪明点的问题
Why don't you try asking me a smart- person question?
考智力的 比如但丁的《地狱篇》是谁写的
Something intellectual, like who wrote Dante's Inferno?
很明显就是但丁啊
Well, obviously, that would be Dante.
我举错例子了
Well, that was a bad examplel
马蒂这里一点像样的食物都没有
Ugh. I mean, Marty has no real food here.
你看看这个
I mean, would you look at this?
就几张绿色的纸
Just pieces of green paper.
那是海苔
That's seaweed
他还花了8.99美元买的
And he paid $8. 99 for it
这就是海滩上的垃圾啊
This is nothing but beach garbage.
有那钱买包鸡腿肉
For that price, I dould have bought
不好吗
a pack of chicken thighs.
卡尔文 我知道跟人合伙很不客易
Calvin, look, I know itls hard having a partner.
你爸当初带你进维修厂 领你入行时
Like when your dad brought you into the business
不也一样吗
at the Pit Stop.
别让我提起那男人
Oh, do not get me started about that man.
他是倔驴脾气 还墨守成规
He was stubborn and stuck in his ways.
不是 好吧 我知道你啥意思了
No. Okay, no. I see what you're doing here,
但这能一样吗
but this is different. You know?
我当时是想告诉我爸
I was trying to show my dad
如何跟上时代
how to keep up with the times.
这跟我教会马蒂我们一贯的经营方法
Which is not the same as me trying to show Marty
是不一样的
how we did things in the past.
就是不一样
It's- it's just different. That's all.
-我什么也没说  -我知道
I didn't say a word. I know.
但是你的脸已经说出了一切
But your face is very loud.
听着 卡尔文 我们很幸运
Look, Calvin, we're blessed.
我们刚庆祝完你们八个月来的首次盈利
We just celebrated your first profit after eight months.
这多难得啊
That never happens.
70%的创业公司都会失败
70%of new businesses fail.
所以 不管这些小怪胎在于啥
So whatever these little weirdos are doing,
明显很见成效 宝贝
clearly it's working, baby.
所以呢 你想让我当甩手掌柜
So, what, you just want me to sit back
看着他们把我变成富豪吗
and let them make me rich?
我听到你的表情了 不用回答
No, I heard your face. Don't worry about it.
No, I heard your face. Donlt worry about it.
嘿 珍
Hey, Gem.
我现在成“太太”了
It's"ma'am"now.
别这样 杰玛 你不是太太
Come on, Gemma you are not a ma'am.
你跟太太完全不一样
You are the opposite of a ma'am.
这么说我是先生了
Oh, so I'm a sir.
我谢谢你了 好吧
Thanks a lot. Okay.
Thanks a lot Okay
珍玛别这样
Gemma. Gemma come on.
是 你儿子都进青春期了
So you have a teenager now.
那又怎样 你依然很性感
So what? You are still hot.
对 辣的冒烟 你知道吗
Yeah, you're fire. You know that?
Yeah, youfre fire. You know that?
你穿上瑜伽裤美爆了
You look great in yoga pants.
即便穿着没洗的运动裤
Even now in these dirty sweatpants
顶着一头乱糟糟的头发
with your with your messy hair
巧克力弄得满脸都是
and- and chocolate all over your face.
对 不 对 下面一点
Yeah, that's...No. Yeah, that's right. Down there.
不对
No, now you're-
都被你舔到脖子上了
Now you're spreading it onto your neck.
好了 听着 停下 求你了
Okay, look, stop. Just stop it, please.
珍玛 重点是 你依然很性感
Gemma, the point is, you are smoking hot,
外面那些混蛋全错了
and those jerks out there are all wrong.
抱歉 我没想这么咄咄逼人的
Sorry, that was way more aggressive than I intended.
各位 我有点好奇
Uh, hey, guys, just curious.
你看到一个漂亮的金发女郎
Have you seen a gorgeous blonde woman
-走进那房子了吗  -看到了
go in that house? Yeah.
那你怎么啥都不说
Yeah. Well, then why the hell haven't you said anything?
我不懂你在说什么
I don't follow.
好吧 你们是建筑工人
Okay, you guys are construction workers,
Okay, you guys are construction workers.
你们就该对着女生吹口哨
You're supposed to cat call women.
那个女人是我妻子
That was my wife, and
你伤害了她的感情
you hurt her feelings.
我们应该尊重女性的
We're supposed to be respectful.
不不 你不应该
No No, you're not.
你下次看到我老婆
Next time you see my wife,
千万别喊她太太
keep the word"ma'am"out your mouth.
其实也不是我们的错
It's not us.
人事给我们开过会
We had an HR seminar
说是要营造健康的工作场所
on fostering a healthy workplace.
相信我 你老婆辣到冒烟
Believe me, your wife is a smoke show.
谢谢你能这么说
Thank you for saying that.
另外 语气别这么激动
Also, dial it back.
嘿 小伙子
Hey, hey, little buddy.
我得问问
I got to ask.
你这种男人是怎么泡到这种美女的
How did a guy like you get a woman that hot?
你一定很有钱吧
You got to be rich, right?
你是搞加密币的吗
Are you one of those crypto guys?
不 我不是搞加密币的
No, I'm not one of those crypto guys.
我长得也很帅 人也很有趣
I'm very good- looking and I'm funny.
财务上也还说得去
And financially, I do just fine.
好事 先生
Good for you, sir.
戴夫 你在干吗啊
Dave, what are you doing?
我这就有点看不懂了
Now I don't know anymore.
因为据他们所说 你性感到冒烟
According to them, you're smoking hot,
而我
and I'm
我只是个普通的矮矬穷
I'mjust some homely troll.
他们说我性感
They called me hot?
哦 真贴心
Oh, that's sweet.
哼 臭流氓
You guys are pigs!
fusebox
耶 上分了 小弱鸡
Oh, booml Game, sucker.
哈哈 耶
Ha ha! Yeah.
我要回去工作了
I'm going to go back to work.
真的吗 考特尼
Oh, really, Courtney?
你怎么一输球就说自己要工作呢
Now that you start losing, all of a sucldlen you got to work?
知道吗 我不喜欢跟转杆子的人比赛
You know what? I don't like playing against people who spin.
说得对 就得转杆子啊
You damn right I spin.
你不会转杆子怎么赢球呢
You gotta spin to win.
行 那我们走着瞧 赢不起
Well, this ain't over, spinner.
你是想说“赢家”吧
I think you mean"winner.
不错啊 爸爸 拥抱公司文化了
Well, check you out, Dad. Embracing the culture.
我把整个公司文化都虐惨了
Oh, I am beating the culture's ass.
马蒂 我知道你为什么喜欢这些人了
You know, Marty, I see why you like these people.
他们好有趣啊 对吧 卡尔文
They're fun. Right, Calvin?
是的 你知道 我
Yeah. You know, I
之前可能有点武断了
could have been a little judgmental.
虽然我不常犯错 但真犯错了
And on those rare occasions when I'm not right,
我也会听我合伙人的话
I've learned to defer to my partner,
他一直都做得很好 伙计
who has been doing a great job, man.
谢谢 爸
Thanks, Dad.
谁来掐我下
Somebody pinch me.
所以 那个怀孕的女生是谁
So, who's the pregnant girl?
所 那个怀孕的女生是谁
你说谁怀孕了
Who are you talking about?
那边那个 怀孕的那个啊
That girl right there. The pregnant one.
等等 她指的是
No. Is she pointing at
不不不 因为她
No, no, no no. Cause she
她根本不知道自己在说什么
she doesn't know what she's talking about.
我不知道什么
I don't know what?
不好说哈 孩儿们
I don't know, guys.
你妈一眼就能看出谁怀孕了
Your mother has an amazing baby- dar.
这种天赋蛮奇怪的
It's a weird talent.
我们一直在琢磨
We've been trying to figure out
怎么把它变现
how to monetize it.
等等等等 你啥意思
Wait, wait, wait. What are you saying?
你是说考特尼怀孕了
Are you saying Courtney's pregnant?
考特尼
Courtney?
她就是考特尼
That's Courtney?
-是的  -你的考特尼
Yes. Your Courtney?
是的
Well...Yes.
你没有 不会吧
Did you No, no, no, no.
你不会是说那个女孩怀孕了吧
You better not tell me that you got that girl pregnant!
等一下 你要是有了宝宝
Wait a minute. If you're having a baby,
那意味着我当奶奶了
that means I'm a grandma.
-好紧张啊  -是的
I'm a little nervous. Yeah.
-但也很兴奋  -是的
But I'm excited. Yeah.
紧张和兴奋交织在一起
So I guess I'm nervous- skited.
-但是我对你很失望  -嗷 嗷
But I'm very disappointed in you! Ow, ow, ow!
-我都不知该作何感想了  -冷静一下
Ijust don't know how to feel. Calm down.
妈妈 你又不确定啊
Mom, you don't know that.
那就去问问她啊
Well, then, go ask her.
妈 我不能直接跑去问一姑娘怀孕了没
Mommy, I can't ask a woman if she's pregnant.
-我可以  -不
Well, I can. No
宝贝
Babe. Babe. Babe
-爸 你做点什么吧  -等等 等等
Daddy, please do something. Whoa, whoa, whoa.
停 妈妈 妈妈
Stop, Mama! Mama...
求你不要
Please, please, please...Please don't.
嘿 亲爱的 你还好吗
Hey, sweetie How you doing?
我很好啊 B太太
I'm good, Mrs. B.
知道吗 你皮肤好好啊
Oh. You know, you have beautiful skin.
散发着光晕
You're glowing.
谢谢
Thank you.
昨天杂货店一女的
You know a woman in the grocery store
也这么说来着
told me that yesterday?
那肯定
I bet.
你在吃什么呀
So, what you got there?
哦 五花肉和酸奶
Oh, chicharrones and yogurt.
我知道这么吃很奇怪 可就是停不下来
I know it's weird, but I can't stop eating it.
你知道吗 太好吃了
Um, you know So good.
我觉得 我们需要谈谈
I think we need to talk.
-好吧  -所以
Oh. Okay. Yeah. So
-好吧   -所以
Oh. Okay. Yeah. So...
里面究竟什么情况
MARTY: What is happening in there?
让你妈施展魔力 好吗
Oh, no, just let your mama do her thing, all right?
大家淡定点 冷静
Everybody just chill. Calm down.
-都给我淡定  -但究竟发生了什么
Everybody chill out! Just chill out! But what is happening?
好吧
Okay. Uh- oh. Uh- oh.
Okay. Uh oh. Uh oh.
-考特尼在哭  -不是 这也不代表什么啊
Courtney's crying. Oh, no. But that can mean anything.
-但你妈在笑  -即便如此呢
But your mama's smiling. Even so. Even so.
天 你有麻烦了
Oh, you in trouble.
你能花9刀买海苔
So you can buy a nine- dollar bag of seaweed,
都不愿花2刀买避孕套
but can't buy a two- dollar condom?